DIXON GILLETTE: In three, two, one.
Okay.
Now, we're going to talk about laying parallel track and building switches.
Most of the time, you're going to need to build parallel track because you're just going to be having too many operations being conducted at your city depot centers.
So, to lay parallel track, we're going to select our Double Track icon here or push D on the keyboard.
Again, you can see it highlights the track that you currently own.
Again, you're going to see your mouse pointer change into your circle colors depending on the type of operation that you are performing.
So to begin laying parallel track, you're going to want to bring your mouse pointer directly beside the track that you want to lay, and we'll just zoom it a little bit here.
And as you can see here, we now have a green chevron.
Now, to begin laying the track, left-click on your mouse once to begin the start point and then simply drag your track alongside the other track.
Once you're satisfied with its length, left-click again and, as you can see, you've just completed parallel track building.
Now, from there, we can build a switch.
To build a switch, we're going to want to push our Single Track icon or T on the keyboard, and we're going to want to drag our mouse pointer over the edge of our parallel track.
Now, you're going to want to click once there and drag this to an interior portion of your other track.
Now, as you can see, you have a yellow indicator there, and that's telling you essentially that you are building on an interior portion of your track.
So what we're going to do is once we're happy with each position, we are going to left-click again, and it will build the switch.
And now, as you see, in its place, there is now a signal, so now trains can utilize both of these tracks and your routing will become all the more efficient.